<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Nigga</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="first_year">First_year</string>
    <string name="open">open</string>
    <string name="close">close</string>
    <string name="messageToMyBaby">Hey baby,
        \n\n Anniversaries are meant to be celebrated, For us
        \nOur Anniversary serves as a happy reminder of how far God has brought us
        \n and that we will spend the rest of our lives together.
        \Now, then and forever.
    </string>
    <string name="my_nigga">My Nigga</string>
    <string name="pause">PAUSE</string>
    <string name="play">PLAY</string>

    <string name="to_my_baby">Hey baby,
        \n\n Two years basking in the euphoria of love with my soul mate, I couldn\'t have asked for a better
        \n partner order than you. babe, you are my missing rib and i am glad i found you, against all odds,
        \n how we met will always be a mystery to me but i would never forget the first time i set my eyes on you,
        \n it was a confirmation of a journey i didn\'t know was awaiting us.
        \n Being with you has been nothing short of blessings, joy and happiness. Yea, we have our dispute, arguments, fights
        \n but all these only makes me love you more and be the right man for you. No matter how much we fight, i still
        \n always look forward to hearing your voice, i always want to apologize for whatever might have caused it, i just want to make it right
        \n with you at that very moment. The last 2 years with you has been a memorable one and i anxiously look forward to the years
        \n ahead when i make it official with you, I LOVE YOU and i have never regretted this decision of loving you unconditionally,
        \n sometimes i get scared of how far i can go to make you happy cos as they say a person in love is usually deaf and blind to his surrounding,
        \n but with you, it\'s a safe place and i feel so lucky to be your man and you my Lady.
        \n\n Wow, 2 years and counting in a relationship filled with love, commitment and positive energy in constant improvement everyday, i am actually typing this and
        \n it\'s not a fantasy but a reality, I have always wanted an ego-free relationship with the absence of pride and distrust along side a best friend, a crazy friend,
        \n gist partner, aproko partner, lol and a partner in crime and God has blessed me with you Boluwatife Abioye. The time spent together in bashorun still remains my
        \n most cherished memory with the highest value during my NYSC days. Reading through our old chat brings smile to my face, it reminds me of the foundation of this
        \n Wholesome, Awesome and Beautiful relationship journey we embark on till forever. "femiiiiiiiiiiiii" is the very first message in our chat nd my reply "Boluuuuuuu"
        \n was my first reply and first message to you, tell me which intro beats that. (i need those emoji\'s to be inserted here, unfortunately i can\'t) lol. and the chat went
        \n on to defile all odds of distance and differences which has metamorphosed into an inseparable unity garnished with uncontrollable love and understanding, our relationship
        \n wouldn\'t be complete without God, the author of this beautiful union. I always thank God for sending me a helper, an angel, a life partner i would forever cherish.
        \n\n Never have i had a doubt about what we share, what i feel for you, yea, i am not perfect but i am trying everyday to be better than i was the previous day, i have traumas
        \n from bad experiences in previous relationship and to be honest your love, care and commitment has helped me through them, i have been a believer that not every lady/woman are the
        \n same, you came my way and you are the answer and confirmation to that believe. I have loved you from the first day, i have loved you before this shy boy even walked up to you to say
        \n "hi bolu", i have loved you even before i asked you to be mine, i wasn\'t the first, second or even third, i wasn\'t even the best person of all your suitors, but you gave me a chance
        \n and i hope you haven\'t regretted it with my actions in this past 2 years, if so, i promise you won\'t regret it ever, if not, I want you to know, i am working tirelessly to be a better
        \n person and make it up to you for the things i have done to hurt you in anyway. My unwavering love for you Bolu, will continue to grow stronger by the second, minute, hours, days, weeks,
        \n months, years and forever as long as God lives.
        \n\n How you pull my short when i try to put it on and i run around the room is one thing i can\'t stop myself from smiling every time i reminisce on those moments in bashorun, how you pollute
        \n and hold me down to not leave instead take it in like a man.. lmao.. how you smile, i can\'t get tired of that smile, i can stay all day staring at that beautiful face glowing with that bright
        \n smile. "Babe what are we eating this night", those days, i really look forward to them and i can feel how close we are to sharing those moments together again. I honestly want to jump into the
        \n future with you but the process makes it more beautiful, the ups and downs, Yea, we are far from being perfect but no one can take what we share and how we feel away from us.
        \n\n Hey, Hope you are enjoying the song iyawo mi cos this is for you sweetheart and this app is made specially for you. I hope you love it, it\'s the least i could do cos u have been supportive from
        \n the day you knew what i was into and what i wanted, i got here and u are still my support system, thanks to God for giving me a beautiful and understanding soul, you are my answered prayers.
        \n\n Babe, it\'s now difficult for me to imagine my life without you in it, i mean just trying to imagine if i hadn\'t met you doesn\'t even look possible anymore and it sure doesn\'t feel right too,
        \n lol. Remembering the early days, sitting in front of your office at secretariat gisting and walking the whole environment together, it feels so great and captivating, every bit of it. How we talked
        \n about our fears and our pasts. Talking to you has always brought warmth and comfort, being with you has always been peaceful from the very first day, sorry if you can\'t say the same with me but trust
        \n me babe, i will always be better than a day old me, and i will be the kinda guy an amazing woman like you truly deserves.
        \n\n Babe, you are an angel sent by God into my life, your unwavering support and love towards me keeps me going from sunrise to dusk, you are an answered prayer, as i said, we may argue, fight, have differences,
        \n this is common in even the most beautiful marriage but it doesn\'t make me love you less. and i want you to know you are perfect the way you are, I Love you for everything you are and i promise to make you proud
        \n of the choice you made to be with me.
        \n I earnestly look forward to our marriage, i know our children will thank me for giving them a wonderful mother, at least i am sure to raise my shoulder to that, lol
        \n Spending forever with you is a lifetime accomplishment, every morning i tell God you are the one i want and i have no doubt He would grant our request.
        \n\n I Know our relationship is far from perfect but i\'m proud of you cos you are perfect to me, so proud of what we have achieved the past few years. I remember how we stated what we wanted in a relationship
        \n and i am happy we can proudly say all we asked of each other is still what we share, you are my best friend, my bae, my nigga and i look forward to making you my wife officially. Going into marriage with you
        \n means we are leading every obstacles ahead of us 1 - 0, with God on our side we are already victorious.
        \n\n I found a Gem, a rare Gem when i found you and i am not losing it. Amen.
        \n And I want to apologize for every wrong i have made, every wrong impression i have created, every shameful memory i have registered in your mind, i hope all of those fade away in no time and you see me as the
        \n boy you fell in love with 2 years back in a better and transformed man, your man you can always be proud of. I am sorry and i am working on making this relationship blissful and a happy one as it has always
        \n been.
        \n\n To the most beautiful woman who has given me a reason to love and to be loved, I wish us a Happy Anniversary and may God continue to uphold us and strengthen our hearts with unconditional love towards each other
        \n as we grow older in this journey to forever. I pray this relationship will blossom into a successful and fruitful marriage in Jesus name. Amen.
        \n\n Cheers to forever baby…
        \n\n Thank you for all that you do sweetheart,
        \n\n I love you soooooooo much.
        \n\n Happy Anniversary to us baby love.

    </string>
</resources>